Kheel, Theodore W. Additional Files. 6021/010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Madison Square Garden, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Kheel, TW RE: Personal Maysles Films, Inc., 1986 (Box 47, Folder 26)
- YWK RE: Carl McCall for Lt. Governor Correspondence and Memos, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 27)
- McCrary, Tex RE: Patricia Duff, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 28)
- McCrary, Tex - Dilenschneider Group RE: DGI, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 29)
- McCrory Corp. - IBJ Schroder Bank and Trust, 1985-1988 (Box 47, Folder 30)
- McDonald, Charles RE: Metro, NET, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 31)
- TWK - Merlin Correspondence and Memos (Box 47, Folder 32)
- Meechan, Frank - Patent, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 33)
- Chris Melteson - Directors Guild correspondence and Memos, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 34)
- TWK - Merlin Drafts, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 35)
- TWK - Merlin n.d. Notes (Box 47, Folder 36)
- TWK - Merlin Agreements, 1982-1983 (Box 47, Folder 37)
- Metropolitan Opera, 1995-2000 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Metropolitan Transportation Authority - corresp. + Testimony, 1971-1975 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Michaan, Steven RE: International Reservation Services, Ltd., 1995 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Midtown Realty Owners Assoc., Inc. Mid-Manhattan Project (Kopple), 1951 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Midway Leasing - ATU Local 1181-1061 Johnson, Horace, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Singh, Ishwari (proposal), 2003 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Breast Cancer Awareness Event (Mitch Gaynor), 2002 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous IMG Licensing, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous - Project on Ethic relations, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous n.d. Notes, etc. (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Morton, Rev. James Parks The Interfaith Center of New York, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Murdock vs. Felker Correspondence and Memos, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Murdock vs. Felker Litigation Binder, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Murdock vs. Felker - Copies, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Murdock vs. Felker Newspaper Clippings (Box 49, Folder 15)
- NBC, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- National Center for Consumers of Legal Services, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Nationwide Legal Services, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- National Football League - constitution + Bylaws, 1968-1974 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- NFL - General Grievances, 1968-1971 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- NFL - Grievances Duplicates + Drafts, 1968-1972 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- NFL - Grievances, Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- NFL Collective Bargaining Negotiations - Positions, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- NFL Collective Bargaining Negotiations - Neutral Physicians, 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- NFL Collective Bargaining Negotiations - Letter to Neutral Physicians, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- NFL Collective Bargaining Negotiations - Licensing, 1968-1971 (Box 49, Folder 26)
- NFL Collective Bargaining Negotiations - NY Times, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- NFL - Detroit Lions Active Players, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 28)
- NFL Standard Players Contract, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 29)
- National Urban League, 2001-2002 (Box 49, Folder 30)
- National Urban League (Hugh Price), 1996 (Box 49, Folder 31)
- Newspaper Dispute Correspondence + Memos, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Newspaper Dispute Newspaper Clippings, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Newspaper Dispute, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Newspaper Dispute NY News + Newspaper Guild, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Newspaper dispute, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Newspaper Industry - Arbitration Correspondence + Memos, 1975-1977 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Newspaper Industry - Abritrations Awards - Originals, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Newspaper Industry - Arbitrations Awards - Copies, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Newspaper Industry - Arbitrations TWK Notes and Drafts, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Newspaper Industry - Arbitrations - Daily News, 1991-2005 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Newspaper Industry - Newspaper Guild of New York correspondence, 1966-1982 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Newspaper Industry - Newspaper Guild of New York Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Newspaper Industry - Newspaper Guild of New York New York News Pension Plan, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Newspaper Industry - Newspaper Guild of New York New York times Mediation, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Newspaper Industry - Newspaper Guild of New York Long Island Press - RE: General file, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Newspaper Industry - Newspaper Guild of New York Amsterdam News, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- International Typographical Union Printers Home, 1984-1987 (Box 50, Folder 17)
- New York News Inc. and New York Newspaper Printing Pressman - Union No. 2 - Arbitration, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- New York News Inc. and New York Newspaper Printing Pressman - Union No. 2 - Arbitration correspondence, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 19)
- New York News Inc. and New York Newspaper Printing Pressmen - Union No. 2 - arbitration Agreements, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 20)
- New York News Inc. and New York Newspaper Printing Pressmen - Union No. 2 - arbitration Copies + Drafts, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- News York News Inc. and New York Newspaper Printing Pressman Union No. 2 - Arbitration Notes and Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 22)
- New York News, Inc. + Tribune Company v. Newspaper + Mail Deliveries Union of NY + Vicinity et al. Legal Binder (Folder 1), 1991 (Box 50, Folder 23)
- New York News, Inc. and Tribune Company v. Newspaper + Mail Deliveries Union of NY + Vicinity et al. Legal Binder - Appeal (folder 2), 1991 (Box 50, Folder 24)
- National News Council/NY Magazine - Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- National News Council / NY Mag - Complaint + Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- National News Council / NY Mag - Article, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- National News Council / NY Mag - Misc. Publications, 1971-1979 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Technical trade School - Newspaper Apprentice Pressmen Correspondence Course, 1958 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Newspaper Strike - correspondence + Memos, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Newspaper Strike - Record Binder, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Newspaper Strike New York Newspaper Guild Press Release + clippings, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Newspaper Strike - Notes, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Drafts, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Newspaper Strike - Matson Information, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Newspaper Strike - Times Info, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- North Shore Towers, Pension Refund - Locals 32B, 32 J Correspondence and Memos, 1974-1982 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- North Shore Towers, Pension Refund - Locals 32B 32J Notes and Drafts, 1975-1998 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- North Shore Towers, Pension Refund - Locals 32B 32J Legal Fees, 1976-1978 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- North Shore Towers, Pension Refund - Locals 32B, 32J Miscellaneous, 1974-1981 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- North Shore Towers Agreements, 1973-1980 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- North Shore Towers, Arbitration and Court Papers, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- NYNN Working List, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Draft Agreement Between Nurture New York's Nature, Inc. and CUNY, 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- NNYN Files - RE: CAF Grant, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- The Birds of Central Park (Rosane, David) Correspondence, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- The Birds of Central Park (Rosane, David) Financials, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- the Birds of Central Park ( Rosane, David) book Presentation, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- The Birds of Central Park (Rosane, David) Terry Tempest Williams and David Rosane Agreement, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- The Birds of Central Park (Rosane, David) Agreement w/ CERC n.d. (Box 52, Folder 14)
- The Birds of Central Park (Rosane, David) Articles, 2002-2005 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Nurture New York's Nature, Inc. Miscellaneous Presentation (Folder 1), 2002-2004 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- nurture New York's Nature, Inc. Miscellaneous Presentation (Folder 2), 2002-2004 (Box 52, Folder 17)
- NNYN General correspondence, 2002-2006 (Box 52, Folder 18)
- NYN Mission Statement n.d. (Box 52, Folder 19)
- NNYN TASC Agreement w/ NNYN, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 20)
- NNYN RE: Notes, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 21)
- NYN - Minutes, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 22)
- NNYN RE: General Info, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 23)
- NNYN Brochures, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 24)
- NNYN Sister Cities Program, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 25)
- NNYN Urban Nature Media Workshop, Inc. (EIN #), 2005 (Box 52, Folder 26)
- NYNN NY Times Advertising/ General Info, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 27)
- NYNN The Museum of the City of New York, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 28)
- NNYN - Summary of Projects Exclusive Beneficiary License Bound Book, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- NNYN - New Yorker Article, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Time Warner NNYN, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- NNYN Promotional material, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- NNYN - Meeting Schedule The Nature of New York - fall, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- The Nature of New York: Its Natural history Environment Curriculum Binder, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  Fall
- The Nature of New York: Its Natural History environment Curriculum Binder Folder 2 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- The Nature of New York Its Natural History Environment Curriculum Binder Folder 3 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- New York City Transit Authority - Robert Love Sick Leave Pay, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  June 12
- New York city Transit Authority Local 100, TWU June 12, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100 TWU, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100 TWU, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  July 9
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100 TWU, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  Aug 4
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100 TWU, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  Aug 7
- New York City Transit authority Seniority in Connection w/ Consolidation of IND-IRT-BMT, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100 TWU, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  Sept 15
- NYC Transit Authority RE: Lunch money for unplanned overtime, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100 TWU, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  Oct 13
- NYC Transit Authority Local 100 TWU, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  Nov 13
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100 TWU, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100 TWU (Seniority of Employees in 147th + 207th merger), 1959 (Box 53, Folder 21)
- New York City Authority Amalgamated Assoc. of Street, Electric, Railway, + Motor Coach Employees of America, Div. 726, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 22)
- New York City Transit Authority Amalgamated, Etc., Local Div. No. 1056, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  Dec 15
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  Jan 12
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  Jan 26
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 26)
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100 TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  Feb 29
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  March 25
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  April 5
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 30)
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, United Motormen's Division, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 31)
- New York City Transit authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 32)
- NYC Transit Authority amalgamated, etc., Division 1056, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  May 12
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  May 13
- New York City Transit Authority Discrimination re: Overtime - Dennis Murray, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 35)
- New York City Transit Authority Differential Pay - William G. Lilienthal, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 36)
- New York City Transit Authority local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  June 2
- New York City Transit Authority Leroy Jackson - Sick Leave Pay, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 38)
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 39)
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 40)
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 41)
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  Aug 16
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 43)
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  Oct 19
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  Oct 20
- New York City Transit authority Ralph DiMichele/Louis J. Maccario, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 46)
- New York City Transit authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 47)
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  Nov 7
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 49)
  Dec 2
- NYC Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 50)
  Dec 9
- NYC Transit Authority Local Div. 1056 - Amalgamated Association of street, Electric, Railway, etc., 1960 (Box 53, Folder 51)
- NYC Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 52)
  Dec 23
- NYC Transit Authority Local Div. 100 - Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric, Railway, etc. and Local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 53)
- NYC Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  Jan 25
- NYC Transit Authority Hyman Rifkin, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- NYC Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- NYC Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- NYC Transit Authority (folder 1) Local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  March 14
- NYC Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- NYC Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  April 10
- NYC Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  May 2
- NYC Transit Authority Salvatore Miano, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- New York City Transit Authority Local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- New York City Transit Authority Bernard Mauer, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- NYCTA local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  Sept 26
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- NYCTA local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- NYCTA Paul J. Cuva, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 17)
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 18)
- NYCTA Local Div. 1056 - Amalgamated Association, etc., 1961 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  Oct 5
- NYCTA Local Div. 726 - Amalgamated Association etc., 1961 (Box 54, Folder 20)
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  Oct 18
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU - Kenneth Goldenberg, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 22)
- NYCTA Raymond J. Peters, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 23)
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 24)
- NYCTA local 100, TWU, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 25)
- NYCTA Mario A. Cuozzo, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 26)
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 27)
- NYCTA Melvin C. Parkes, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 28)
- NYCTA Local Div. 1056 - Amalgamated Association of Steel E.R. and M.C.E. of A., 1962 (Box 54, Folder 29)
- NYCTA local 100, TWU, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 30)
- NYC Transit Authority Alfred Dagri, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  May 15
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  May 16
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 33)
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 34)
  June 4
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 35)
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 36)
- NYC Transit Authority Salvatore Petrone, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 37)
  July 10
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 38)
  July 24
- NYCTA Pasqualle Mignone, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 39)
- NYCTA Pasquale Mignone, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 40)
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 41)
  Aug 10
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 42)
  Sept 21
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 43)
- NYCTA Robert Love, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 44)
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 45)
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 46)
  Oct 25
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 47)
- NYCTA Local 100, TWU, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 48)
  Dec 28
- NY Press Club - Newsmaker Breakfasts, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 49)
- OPIC Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 54, Folder 50)
- OPIC Financials, 1985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 51)
- OPIC - Investment Finance Handbook, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 52)
- OPIC Agreements, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 53)
- Pari Passu Legal documents, 1985-1988 (Box 54, Folder 54)
- Pari Passu (Copy) Corporate Books, Raoul Garino, Inc. - Pari Passu, Inc. (Box 54, Folder 55)
- Pari Passu Corporate Information, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 56)
- Pari Passu, Inc. Tax Documents, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 57)
- Pari Passu General correspondence File, 1983-1986 (Box 54, Folder 58)
- Pari Passu Mortgage with Bankers Trust (Box 54, Folder 59)
- Pari Passu Promissory Note, Bankers Trust 250000 Repayment Letter (Box 54, Folder 60)
- Pari Passu Agreement between Kheel and Lambrou (Box 54, Folder 61)
- Pari Passu Release from Timothy Smith (Box 54, Folder 62)
- Pari Passu Assignment of Lease and Consent of Landlord (Box 54, Folder 63)
- Pari Passu Agreement between Garino, Kheel and Garino, 1983-1988 (Box 54, Folder 64)
- Pari Passu Corporate Name Change: Raoul Garino, Inc. to Pari Passu, Inc., 1985 (Box 54, Folder 65)
- Pari Passu Contract with Chris Katenis, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 66)
- Pari Passu Certificate of Doing Business as Pari Passu, Inc., 1983 (Box 54, Folder 67)
- Pari Passu Memorandum of Lease for Recording, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 68)
- Pari Passu Unrecorded Mortgage on Pari Passu, Inc. - Leasehold, 1985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 69)
- NYC Transit II: Transit Labor Board Agreements, 1966-1979 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- NYC Transit II: Transit Labor board Reports, 1950-1963 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- NYC Transit II: Transit Labor Board Correspondence + Memoranda (Box 55, Folder 3)
- NYC Transit Correspondence, 1946 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- NYC Transit II: Transit Labor board - Report on the Operations of the Impartial Chairman, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- NYC Transit II: Transit Labor Boards Proposals, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- NYC Transit II: Transit Labor Board Drafts, 1960-1966 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- NYC Transit II: Transit Labor Board - Union Demands, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- NYC Transit II - Transit Labor Board - Notes + Working Papers, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- NYC Transit II - Transit Labor Board Clippings, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- NYC Transit II - Transit Labor Board - Exhibits for Contract Negotiations, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- NYC Transit II - Transit Labor Board - Exhibits for contract negotiations, 1959-1961 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- NYC Transit I - Transit Labor board - Agreements (Folder 1), 1944-1966 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- NYC Transit II - Transit Labor board - Agreements folder 2 (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Pari Passu Lease Agreement Between Estate Herman Philips and La Cocotte, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Pari Passu Title Search, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Pari Passu Application for approval of Corporate Change, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Pari Passu Agreement between Herman Philips, N.A. Foods, and Raoul Garino, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Pari Passu RE: Life Insurance for Garino and Kheel, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Pari Passu RE: State of New York Liquor License, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Pari Passu Corporate Banking Resolution and Promissory Note, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Pari Passu RE: Loan with Bankers Trust Company, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Pari Passu Notice of Meeting of Shareholders, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Pari Passu Menus, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Pari Passu Personnel, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Pari Passu Publicity, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Pari Passu Architectural Services, 1983-1984 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Pari Passu, Raoul Garino, Inc. Cash Position, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- Pari Passu, Raoul Garino, Inc. Copies of W-2's, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 15)
- Pari Passu, Raoul Garino, Inc. New York state Department of Labor Tax Compliance, 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 16)
- Pari Passu, Raoul Garino, Inc. US Department of Labor, RE: Checks for Back (Box 56, Folder 17)
- Pari Passu, Raoul Garino, Inc. Workmen's comp Claim RE: Robert Pilbin, 1983-1985 (Box 56, Folder 18)
- Parks + Recreation commission - Ann S Kheel, 1977-1978 (Box 56, Folder 19)
- Participatory Planning August/Correspondence Conference, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 20)
- Participatory Planning - Follow Up Participatory Planning Conference Correspondence, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  Oct 21-23
- Participatory Planning - Follow Up Participatory Planning conference Invites Flight Info, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 22)
- PERC (Prevention + Early Resolution of Conflict) correspondence, 1996-2005 (Box 56, Folder 23)
- PERC - Correspondence File (Folder 1), 1994-1996 (Box 56, Folder 24)
- PERC - Correspondence File (Folder 2), 1995 (Box 56, Folder 25)
- PERC (Prevention + Early Resolution of Conflict) RE: Hewlett Theory Centers Meeting, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  March 21-23
- PERC (Prevention + Early Resolution of Conflict) RE: ADR, 1998-2002 (Box 56, Folder 27)
- PERC (Prevention and Early Resolution of Conflict) RE: ADR Plus (Russell White), 1995 (Box 56, Folder 28)
- PERC (Prevention + Early Resolution of Conflict) US Dept. of Labor, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 29)
- PERC (Prevention + Early Resolution of Conflict) RE: IRRA Membership (Tom Kochan), 1999 (Box 56, Folder 30)
- PERC (Prevention + Early Resolution of conflict) Promotional events, 2000-2003 (Box 56, Folder 31)
- PERC (Prevention + Early Resolution of Conflict) - Promotional Brochures (Box 56, Folder 32)
- PERC - Bios/CVs, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 33)
- PERC RE: Deinhardt, Barbara, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 34)
- PERC RE: Ruth Curtis-Resume, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 35)
- PERC (Prevention + Early Resolution of Conflict) TWK's Notes on Conflict Resolution (Box 56, Folder 36)
- PERC (Prevention + Early Resolution of Conflict) RE: Keys to Conflict Resolution, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 37)
- PERC Agreement w/ Metropolitan Corporate Counsel, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 38)
- PERC Strategic Alliance + Cooperation Agreement w/ Pria Waterhouse, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 39)
- PERC Construction Dispute Resolution Steps (Box 56, Folder 40)
- PERC RE: IRS - Proposed Test of Mediation, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 41)
- PERC - Talking Paper for Discussion, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 42)
- PERC: Legal research, 1994-1995 (Box 56, Folder 43)
- PERC - Press Releases (Drafts), 1994-1996 (Box 56, Folder 44)
- PERC Lists, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- PERC Management Politics + Personnel Law, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- PERC's Proposed Publications (Box 57, Folder 3)
- PERC Cocktail Party, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- PERC Agenda - Organizational meeting, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- PERC Lexis Print-Out Stories, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- PERC Operating Agreement between PERC Publications, LLC + Business Research Publications, Inc., 1995-1996 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- PERC: Corporate Documents, 1994-1995 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- PERC - Slides, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- PERC - Articles (Folder 1), 1994-1995 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- PERC Articles 3, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- PERC Articles 2, 1993-1995 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- PERC: Price Waterhouse Brochure, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- PERC RE: Lemuel Boulware (Box 57, Folder 14)
- PERC 101 Statement (Box 57, Folder 15)
- PERC - Application for Tax Exemption, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 16)
- PERC - Mission Statement (Box 57, Folder 17)
- PERC/Cornell - Internet Info, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 18)
- PERC - Press Coverage, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 19)
- PERC - American Arbitration Association, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Cornell/PERC - Brochures, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- PERC Foundation, RE: Cornell Project Correspondence, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- CPR - Institute for Dispute Resolution, 1995-1996 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- PERC Foundation, RE: Cornell Project Summit Press Launch Meeting, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- PERC Foundation - RE: Cornell Project Material RE Cornell (Box 58, Folder 6)
- PERC Foundation - RE: Cornell Project Discussion Papers, 1956 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- PERC Foundation - RE: Pepsi - Cola Co., 1996 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- PERC - Materials on Thomas Donahue, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 9)